http://www.grailsprings.com/privacy

WelcomeGrail Springs RetreatTestimonialsGrail Gives BackPhilosophyAwardsGrail in the NewsFounderThe Algonquin StoryArticles
Packages & SpecialsGrail Basic PackagesRest & Restore PackagesLife Transformation PackagesSpecial Offers
Plan Your RetreatPreparing for Your RetreatSpa MenuSpa CollectionsSpiritual Enrichment JourneyDay SpaCoachingEquine Meditation
Body-Mind-Spirit7 Keys PhilosophyBioEnergy ReadingsMeditationYogaNutrition
The PropertyThe PropertySpecial FeaturesPhoto Gallery The PropertyPhoto Gallery The InteriorsRooms
ScheduleDaily ScheduleClasses & PresentersGroup Journeys
Shop
Privacy Policy
Grail Springs Privacy Policy
Personal Information: To provide you with our services, inform you of updates and specials, Grail Springs requires your e-mail address. Furthermore, we may ask for some optional information on our sign-up page and in periodic opt-in surveys. We use this basic, and optional information, to further tailor our content to your interests. Grail Springs does not collect any personal information that is not expressly provided to us. Additionally, Grail Springs will not disclose your personal information to any third party without your consent, except when necessary to deliver a requested service. Upon request, we will provide you with the information that we maintain about you.
Web Site Usage Information: Likewise, we and some of our partners, may make use of cookies (small text tiles placed on your computer's hard disk by our server). They are used to collect non-personal traffic information such as the number of visits to our site and pages visited. This information will only be used to assess how subscribers are using our services so that we may better serve you. This data will also allow us to manage the functionality of the site. Grail Springs will never use cookies to retrieve information from a computer that is unrelated to our site or services.
Linked Sites: Although Grail Springs may provide links to third party sites, we are not responsible for the content that appears on those sites nor do we endorse these sites. Please review each site's privacy policy to determine their use of information. Security: Grail Springs stores all of the information described above in restricted databases.
Opt-out / Unsubscribe: If we ever send you an email that you did not expressly request, we will provide you with an email address by which you may request to receive no future notices.
Changes to Privacy Policy: Grail Springs may change this privacy policy. Any changes will be reflected on this privacy policy page. If you are concerned about how your information will be used, you should check back at this privacy policy page periodically.
Contact: If you should have any questions about our privacy policy, please contact us.
Directions to Grail Springs
Learn More
Airport Shuttle
Learn More
Quote or Book:
Arrival
Nights
1
2
3
4
5
6
LEAP™
Updates Available: Updates Available: Update available for Picture Gallery Module
Update Now
System
Account Preferences
Appearance
Skins
Add Skin
Configurations
Spaces
SEO Tags
OLD URLs (302/301)
Robots
Sitemap XML Generator
SEO Keywords
Logout
Site
Add Page
Pages
List Pages
Help
37_Blog Content||40_Blog List||84_Calendar of Events||31_Contact Form||74_Custom Button||76_Custom CTA||80_Custom Isotope Grid||90_Custom Search Box||67_Disqus Comments||82_Event Detail||83_Event Header Image||88_Footer Recognition Gallery||64_Form Component||69_HTML||24_Menu||89_Modal Text Module||5_News||92_Package Comparison||93_Package Nights||87_Program Detail||86_Program Listing||79_Promo Item||77_Responsive Image||73_Rotating Masthead||29_Search Box||30_Search Results||91_Spa Choices||75_Static Masthead||7_Text
